Privacy Policy
==============

Our Commitment To Privacy
-------------------------

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

To buy our software you should register with our online registrator providing it with your personal information including name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card number, and expiration date. You can find additional information about our registrator privacy policy at [Digital River Privacy Statement](https://www.mycommerce.com/corporate-policy/). We keep the information pointed above except credit card number and payment details in our database to send registration codes to you.

Neither ChemTable Software, nor its partners do not disclose to any third parties information received when you are registering ChemTable Software products.

We don't share information you provide us with any third parties apart from mentioned above.

As an exception to that policy ChemTable Software may disclose Personal Information only if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to protect and defend the rights or property of ChemTable Software, the sites or the users of ChemTable Software.

Cookies and Visitor Tracking
----------------------------

Our website collects anonymous information about the visitors by using cookies. Cookies are small pieces of information stored on your computer for a pre-defined period of time. The use of cookies allows us to determine visitors’ path on our website, optimize the content and streamline website structures. In addition, cookies allow us to determine first-time and repeat visitors. Cookies set by ChemTable Software contain no personal information.

Modern Web browsers such as Mozilla Firefox, Google Chrome, Apple Safari or Internet Explorer provide means to control the handling of cookies on your computer. You may block all future cookies, clear and delete existing ones at your will. Please note that if you disable cookies, certain minor functionality of our website may not be available to you due to technical limitations. By visiting chemtable.com, you agree to the use of cookies by ChemTable Software as regulated by this Privacy Policy.

Our website uses Google Analytics, a traffic analysis application provided by Google. The use of cookies by Google Analytics is governed by Google’s own Privacy Policy.

Google Analytics collects anonymous information about visitors to our website and their behavior on our online property. Information collected by Google Analytics may include (but is not limited to) referrer data, visitor’s IP address, Web pages visited, and time spent on our website. This information is stored exclusively on Google servers, and is governed by [Google Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en "Google's Privacy Policy"). ChemTable Software uses this information to optimize our website to improve its performance, usability and content.

Products

Company

Support

© 2024 Software Solutions 365 LLC
